Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dailies, Circa 1985 - 2010; Series 13
  - Dailies - DSCC, 1998 February 11; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Dailies - 1869 Valentine's Party, 1998 February 14; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Dailies - Sidewalk.com, 1998 February 24; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Dailies - Women's Committee Meeting, 1998 February 24; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Dailies - School/Dance, 1998 February 27; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Dailies - Timpone Wedding Reception, 1998 Februaryr 28; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Dailies - Reichard Martin Dinner, 1998 March 3; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Dailies - Collier, Shannon, Rill Scott, 1998 March 7; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Dailies - Cardiology Research Foundation, 1998 March 9; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Dailies - New Member Reception, 1998 March 12; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Dailies - American Academy of Allergy Asthma Immunology, 1998 March 13; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Dailies - Ida Opening, 1998 March 14; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Dailies - SBOO/MBOO Gibby's, 1998 March 16; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Dailies - Geico, 1998 March 16; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Dailies - Semi-Conductor Industry Association, 1998 March 17; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Dailies - Bloom Wedding, 1998 March 28; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Dailies - Friends Acquisition, 1998 March 30; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Dailies - John Alcridge Companies, 1998 March 27; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Dailies - New York University, 1998 April 7; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - Dailies - Corcoran Ball, 1998 April 17; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Dailies - PEPCO, 1998 April 21; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Dailies - H.R. Family Evening, 1998 April 21; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Dailies - Annual Student Awards Ceremony, 1998 April 22; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Dailies - H.R./Director's Circle, 1998 April 22; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - Dailies - Friends Tour Reception, 1998 April 23; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - Bechhoefer Dinner at David's, 1998 April 23; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 45)
  - Dailies - Harlem Renaissance Opening, 1998 April 24; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 46)
  - Dailies - Williams Connolly, 1998 April 25; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 47)
  - Dailies - RGA, 1998 April 26; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 48)
  - Dailies - Brooks Brothers Photoshoot, 1998 April 28; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 49)
  - Dailies - Academy of Science, 1998 April 28; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 50)
  - Dailies - Women's Committee BOT Lunch, 1998 April 28; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 51)
  - Dailies - Council on Foundation's Annual Meeting, 1998 Apirl 29; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 52)
  - Dailies - Dinner at David's, 1998 April 30; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 53)
  - Dailies - Office of the SEcretary of Defense, 1998 April 29; Series 13 (Box 72, Folder 54)
  - Asso. General Contractors, 1998 April 27; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Renaissance Symposium, 1998 May 1; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - H.R./Symposium, 1998 May 1; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - West Wedding, 1998 May 2; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Delottie Touche, 1998 May 4; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Union Labor of Life Insurance, 1998 May 4; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Senior Exhibition Opening, 1998 May 5; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - WAMU, 1998 May 6; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Friends Lecture and Reception, 1998 May 7; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1998 May 8; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Marvin Palmer Association Inc., 1998 May 11; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Wechsler, Ross and Partners, 1998 May 13; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - 1869 Reception, 1998 May 14; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - CSA Commencement Reception, 1998 May16; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Board ofo Trustees, 1998 May 18; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1998 May 20; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - NAFSA, 1998 May 27; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1998 June; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Chairman's Lunch, 1998 June 2; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Doocent Luncheon, 1998 June 9; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Department of Education, 1998 June 9; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - O'Melvery Myers, 1998 June 12; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - US Department of Education, 1998 June 15; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Alliance to Save Energy, 1998 June 16; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1998 June 17; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - National Scholastic Art Writing Awards, 1998 June 19; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - KPMG Peat Marwick LLP, 1998 June 19; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - American Society of Pension Actuaries, 1998 June 23; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Dinner at DL's/Shatz, 1998 June 24; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Info Access, 1998 June 28; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Frankenthaler, 1998 June 30; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Asso. of Trial Lawyers, 1998 July 12; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - WAMU, 1998 July 18; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Mayorial Candidates, 1998 July 20; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Director's Circle Biennial, 1998 July 22; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Membership Opening - Biennial, 1998 July 24; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Heifetz International Music Institute, 1998 July 25; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Federal Hiway - E Street, 1998 July 29; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - At Kearney, 1998 July 31; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Service Fees, Circa 1998; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Facility Use, Circa 1998; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Invoices/Purchase Orders, Circa 1998; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - Fee Forms, Circa 1998; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - Documents from Binder, Circa 1998; Series 13 (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - Chase Manhattan, 1998 October 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Brown Brothers, 1998 October 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Reuters, 1998 October 6; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Bankers Trust, 1998 October 6; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Family Day, 1998 October 10; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Director's Circle - Fall, 1998 October 14; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Jeannette Petite Luncheon, 1998 October 15; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - 1869 Reception, 1998 October 15; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Textile Museum, 1998 October 17; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Membership Opening - Fall, 1998 October 16; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Shaw Pittman Potts, 1998 October 17; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Capital One Financial Corporation, 1998 October 19; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - CPC International, 1998 October 20; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Sheehan Wedding Reception, 1998 October 24; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - PBS, 1998 October 26; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee, 1998 October 27; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1998 November; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Choice Hotels, 1998 November 1; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, 1998 November 2; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - School Dance, 1998 November 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - National Metal of Arts Luncheon, 1998 November 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - New Member's Reception, 1998 November 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - 1869 Black Tie Gala, 1998 November 7; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - UUNET Technologies, Inc., 1998 November 9; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - The American Urogynecologic Society, 1998 November 13; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - WPA Corcoran, 1998 November 14; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Hecht's, 1998 November 17; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Salon Dore, 1998 November 18; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - PCMA, 1998 November 19; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Washingtonian (Cancelled), 1998 November 23; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Women's Committee, 1998 November 24; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - ULLICO, 1998 November 30; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Dailies, 1998 December; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - New Israel Fund, 1998 December 1; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Democratic Leadership, 1998 December 2; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Deloitte Touche, 1998 December 5; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - HMC School of Music, 1998 December 6; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - WGMS 103.5, 1998 December 7; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - First National Bank of MP, 1998 December 8; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - AFCEA, 1998 December 9; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Friends Annual Meeting, 1998 December 10; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - FBR, 1998 December 12; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - General Dynamics, 1998 December 13; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - Dewey Ballantine, 1998 December 15; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - Morgan, Lewis Bockius, 1998 December 16; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - Docent Holiday Party, 1998 December 17; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - Watson, Wyatt Company, 1998 December 18; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - Howrey Simon, 1998 December 19; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - Friends of Chris Dodd, 1999 January 6; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - Margenan Wedding Reception, 1999 January 9; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 50)
  - DNC, 1999 January 15; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 51)
  - Bloom/Rose Wedding, 1999 January 17; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 52)
  - 1869 Reception, 1999 January 21; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 53)
  - Ruesch International, 1999 Janaury 23; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 54)
  - Boston University, 1999 January 23 - 1999 Januaryy 24; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 55)
  - Australian Landscapes, 1999 January 25; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 56)
  - Director's Office, 1999 January 25; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 57)
  - Durkee Associates, 1999 January 26; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 58)
  - Women's Committee Meeting, 1999 January 26; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 59)
  - Director's Circle New World From Old, 1999 Janaury 27; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 60)
  - WC Business Professional Luncheon, 1999 January 28; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 61)
  - Membership Opening - Winter, 1999 January 29; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 62)
  - Precision Meeting and Events, 1999 January 30; Series 13 (Box 75, Folder 63)
  - Upscale Tag Sale, 1999 February 1 - 1999 February 2; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Australia America Association, 1999 February 3; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Washington Conservation Guild, 1999 February 4; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Nakian Opening, 1999 February 5; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - AMS, 1999 February 6; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - On Site Productions, 1999 February 9; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 1869 Valentine's Dday Party, 1999 February 13; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Art Forum Luncheon, 1999 February 16; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - John Akridge Companies, 1999 February 19; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Dinner at David's, 1999 February 21; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Women's Committee, 1999 February 23; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - DSCC, 1999 February 24; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - KPMG, 1999 March 1; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Ellsworth, 1999 March 6; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - LeBoeuf, Lamb, Greene MacRae, 1999 March 9; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Dinner at David's, 1999 March 10; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Friends Reception, 1999 March 4; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - International Plazma Products Industry Association, 1999 March 10; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - American College of Bankruptcy, 1999 March 12; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Family Day, 1999 March 13; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Parke Davis/TCI, 1999 March 13; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Geico, 1999 March 15; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Campbell Peachey/Dainler Chrysler, 1999 March 16; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, 1999 March 16; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Occasions Caterers, 1999 March 17; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 1999 March 18; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Dudley Lecture, 1999 March 20; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - National Art Education Association, 1999 March 23; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Embassy of Australia, 1999 March 26; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Wilkins/Kaplan Wedding (Ceremony Reception), 1999 March 27; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Friends Acquisition Evening, 1999 March 29; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Capital City Events, 1999 March 30; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Clark Wedding, 1999 April 10; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - The Chlorine Institute, Inc., 1999 April 12; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Dinner at David's, 1999 April 13; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Amnerican Association of Immunologists/PharMingen, 1999 April 18; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - The Levine School of Music Concerts, 1999; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Swiss American Cultural Exchange Council, 1999 April 23; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - PRTM, 1999 April 26; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Marketing Resources, 1999 April 27; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Annual Student Awards, 1999 April 28; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Atlantic Dermatology Congress, 1999 April 30; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Howar Wedding Reception, 1999 May 1; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - All Senior Exhibition Opening, 1999 May 3; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - AT, 1999 May 4; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Jeanette Petite Luncheon, 1999 May 6; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 46)
  - Federal City Caterer/Children's Scholarship Fund, 1999 May 8; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - MacDonald Communication Corporation, 1999 May 10; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Dinner at David's/Gehry, 1999 May 14; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Reception, 1999 May 15; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 50)
  - Photosound Communications, 1999 May 16; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 51)
  - Organon Inc., 1999 May 17; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 52)
  - American Electronics Assoc., 1999 May 18; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 53)
  - Weschler Ross Partners, 1999 May 19; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 54)
  - Glaxo Welcome, 1999 May 19; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 55)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 1999 May 20; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 56)
  - Association of Corporate Travel Executive, 1999 May 23; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 57)
  - Board of Trustee Dinner, 1999 May 24; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 58)
  - Weiss/Jewel Wedding (Ceremony Reception), 1999 May 30; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 59)
  - Docent Luncheon, 1999 June 1; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 60)
  - Lichtenstein Opening, 1999 June 4; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 61)
  - Georgetown University Class of 1969, 1999 June 5; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 62)
  - Guidant Corporation, 1999 June 8; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 63)
  - O'Melveeny Myers LLP, 1999 June 11; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 64)
  - Art Forum Luncheon, 1999 June 15; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 65)
  - Morrison Foerster, 1999 June 16; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 66)
  - 1869 Happy Hour - M.R. Book Signing, 1999 June 17; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 67)
  - Scholastics, 1999 June 18; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 68)
  - EGR International, 1999 June 19; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 69)
  - Oppenheimer Dinner at D.L.'s, 1999 June 22; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 70)
  - Architectural Selection Committee Reception, 199 June 23; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 71)
  - Chemonics, 1999 June 25; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 72)
  - US Trust (Planned Giving Program), 1999 June 29; Series 13 (Box 76, Folder 73)
  - Carr Wedding, 1999 July 17; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Matthew Bender Co., Inc., 1999 July 19; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Alza Pharmaceuticals, 1999 July 20; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Lexis Nexis, 1999 July 20; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Goldman Sachs Co., 1999 July 26; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - J. Cowart Farewell Dinner at DL, 1999 July 28; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Andersen, 1999 July 30; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1999 August; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - ISES, 1999 August 7; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Wilke Wedding (Ceremony Reception), 1999 August 14; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Dade Behring, 1999 August 16; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Hargrove Wedding, 1999 August 21; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Jones Wedding Reception, 1999 August 28; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1999 September; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - On Site Productions, 1999 September 10; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 1999 September 16; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Chebron, 1999 September 14; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Cardoso Opening, 1999 September 17; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Sony - Lebaron Wedding Reception, 1999 September 19; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - WAMU, 1999 September 21; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - J.P. Professional Business Luncheon, 1999 September 23; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Board Meeting/Reception, 1999 September 24; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Brown Brothers, 1999 September 27; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Goldman Sachs Co., 1999 September 26; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1999 September 27; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - DCCC (on behalf of Ron Abramson), 1999 September 29; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Frieneds Annual Meeting/Reception, 1999 September 30; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1999 October; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - White House Fellows, 1999 October 1; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1999 October 4; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, 1999 October 6; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - McNeil Consumer Products, 1999 October 9; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Wider Opportunity for Women, 1999 October 10; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Stable Value Investment Association, 1999 October 13; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - WPA/Corcoran Auction Opening, 1999 October 14; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Putnam Investments, 1999 October 15; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - Akin Gump, 1999 October 16; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 1999 October 21; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - WPA/Corcoran Auction, 1999 October 23; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Leibovitz Corrporate Preview, 1999 October 25; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - United States - Azerbaijan, 1999 Octoober 25; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Vogue, 1999 October 26; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 42)
  - Women's Committee Event, 1999 October 28; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 43)
  - Director's Circle, 1999 October 29; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 44)
  - Fairfax Symphony Orchestra, 1999 October 30; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 45)
  - Dailies, 1999 November; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 46)
  - Membership Opening, 1999 November 1; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 47)
  - Sam Bookatz Dinner, 1999 November 2; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 48)
  - Truland Systems, 1999 November 3; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 49)
  - 1869 Society Black Tie Gala, 1999 November 6; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 50)
  - Neiman Marcus, 1999 November 9; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 51)
  - Vogue for Mercedez-Benz, 1999 November 12; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 52)
  - Micro-Strategy, 1999 November 14; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 53)
  - PCMA, 1999 November 18; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 54)
  - Clark Attlanta University, 1999 November 23; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 55)
  - The Way Home, 1999 November 29; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 56)
  - Vogue for Concord/Movado, 1999 November 30; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 57)
  - Porter Novelli, 1999 December 3; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 58)
  - Deloitte Touche, 1999 December 4; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 59)
  - All First, 1999 December 7; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 60)
  - Dailies, 1999 December; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 61)
  - AFCEA, 1999 December 8; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 62)
  - KPMG, 1999 December 10; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 63)
  - Freidman, Billing, Ramsey Co., 1999 December 11; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 64)
  - Docent Holiday Party, 1999 December 12; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 65)
  - Dewey Ballantine, 1999 December 14; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 66)
  - Digex Corporation, 1999 December 15; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 67)
  - CGA Holiday Party, 1999 Deecember 16; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 68)
  - Watson Wyatt Worldwide, 1999 December 17; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 69)
  - Howrey Simon, 1999 December 18; Series 13 (Box 77, Folder 70)
  - Vogue for Cole Hahn, 2000 January 7; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Matthew Bender Co., Inc., 2000 January 8; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Art Forum Luncheon, 2000 January 11; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - J.P. Luncheon, 2000 January 12; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - National Alliance - Tour/Lecture/Reception, 2000 January 13; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Focus on Photo Journalism Dinner, 2000 January 14; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - AT, 2000 January 14; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - HBCU Alumni Reception, 2000 January 16; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Tachyon, Inc., 2000 January 18; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - DNC, 2000 January 19; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Tour Guild of Washington, 2000 January 20; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 2000 January 20; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Howard University, 2000 January 21; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Boston University, 2000 January 22 - 2000 January 23; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Make-A-Wish Foundation, 2000 January 22; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - FIVA Reception, 2000 January 28; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Kaplan Wedding (Ceremony and Reception), 2000 January 29; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Chemonics, 2000 February 4; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - PMPI Luncheon, 2000 February 8; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - 1869 Society Valentine's Day Party, 2000 February 12; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - PGI/Marriott, 2000 February 15; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Klemm Birthday Event, 2000 February 21; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - DSCC, 2000 February 23; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - American Red Cross, 2000 February 26; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Palace of Gold Light: Treasures from the Topkapi, Istanbul, 2000 February 29; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - WBENC, 2000 March 1; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Topkapi Corporate Preview, 2000 March 2; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Friends Topkapi Event, 2000 March 3; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Baragona/Wise Wedding Reception, 2000 March 4; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Mortgage Bankers Association of America, 2000 March 6; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - WC Mother-Daughter Luncheon, 2000 March 7; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - J.P. Luncheon, 2000 March 9; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Pension Real Estate Association, 2000 March 15; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Newman/Kurtz Opening Reception, 2000 March 17; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Ruesche International, 2000 March 18; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Geico 1999 Public Service Awards, 2000 March 20; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Starwood Hotels, 2000 March 21; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Greenwell Goetz Architects, 2000 March 22; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - 1869 Happy Hour, 2000 March 23; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - The Turkish Foundation, 2000 March 29; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Moore/Merril Wedding Ceremony and Reception, 2000 April 8; Series 13 (Box 78, Folder 41)